Yemliha Demirdelen

Beykoz, Istanbul, Turkey

yemlihaddln@hotmail.com

+905067790414

linkedin.com/in/yemliha-demirdelen-a7b7ab20

Summary

Experienced Software Engineer with a demonstrated history of working in the information technology and services industry. Skilled in PHP, MySQL, Python, Postgresql, Laravel, Codeigniter, Django, Nodejs, Vue js and Mobile Application Development. Strong engineering professional with a Bachelor's Degree focused in Chemistry from Dokuz Eylul University.

Experience



Full Stack Developer

Lunchbox

Aug 2022 - Oct 2023 (1 year 3 months)

Full Stack Developer

Delish

Feb 2021 - Aug 2022 (1 year 7 months)

Back End Developer

Sigma Telecom LLC

Aug 2020 - Feb 2021 (7 months)

Software Development Specialist

Tele Radio Group

Nov 2019 - Jul 2020 (9 months)

Software Development Specialist

Cenasis Yazılım Hiz. Tic. Ltd. Şti

Nov 2017 - Nov 2019 (2 years 1 month)

Full Stack Developer

Süperpratik

Mar 2017 - Oct 2017 (8 months)

Software Developer

CodeLAB 2014

Aug 2014 - Jan 2017 (2 years 6 months)

Full Stack Developer

Military Technical Support Specialist

Miwisoft

Dec 2013 - Aug 2014 (9 months) Mijosoft LLC www.miwisoft.com

Web Master

www.katana.com.tr Mar 2013 - Dec 2013 (10 months)

Web Designer and Developer

Blueberry, www.hamileyastigim.com Jan 2011 - Jan 2013 (2 years 1 month)

Education

Anadolu University

Öğrenci, Management Information Systems, General Oct 2021 - Present

Dokuz Eylul University

Bachelor's Degree, Chemistry 2005 - 2010

Kadirli Anadolu Lisesi

Kadirli Anadolu Lisesi

Skills

PHP • MySQL • HTML • Cascading Style Sheets (CSS) • JavaScript • Vue.js • Git • Laravel • Codelgniter • Node.js